var questions = [
    {
        question: "Singe line comments start with:",
        choiceOne: "<>",
        choiceTwo: "//",
        choiceThree: "\\",
        choiceFour: "<!-->",
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What is used to declare a JavaScript Value?",
        choiceOne: "var",
        choiceTwo: "variable",
        choiceThree: "iable",
        choiceFour: "function",
        answer: 1
    },
    {
    question: "If a variable is decleared with no value, what happens?",
        choiceOne: "Nothing will happen",
        choiceTwo: "0 will pop up",
        choiceThree: "Variable will have an undefined value",
        choiceFour: "A change within HTML will occur",
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What does + mean in JavaScript?",
        choiceOne: "Multiplication",
        choiceTwo: "Increment",
        choiceThree: "Subtraction",
        choiceFour: "Addition",
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "What does ++ mean in JavaScript?",
        choiceOne: "Decrement",
        choiceTwo: "Increment",
        choiceThree: "Subtraction",
        choiceFour: "Addition",
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What does * mean in JavaScript?",
        choiceOne: "Multiplication",
        choiceTwo: "Increment",
        choiceThree: "Subtraction",
        choiceFour: "Division",
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What does + mean in JavaScript?",
        choiceOne: "Multiplication",
        choiceTwo: "Increment",
        choiceThree: "Subtraction",
        choiceFour: "Addition",
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "How do we find out the length of an array?",
        choiceOne: ".length",
        choiceTwo: ".width",
        choiceThree: "length.size",
        choiceFour: "size.array",
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Where does <script> go?",
        choiceOne: "Within README",
        choiceTwo: "Anywhere in CSS",
        choiceThree: "Body of HTML",
        choiceFour: "Inside script.js",
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What operators do we use to store within arrays?",
        choiceOne: "!!",
        choiceTwo: "//",
        choiceThree: "{}",
        choiceFour: "[]",
        answer: 4
    }
]